18 minutes is an absolutely brutal time limit,
18 минут – очень жестокое ограничение по времени,
so I'm going to dive straight in, right at the point
так что я сразу перейду к существу дела,
where I get this thing to work.
как только эта штука заработает
Here we go. I'm going to talk about five different things.
Готово. Я расскажу о пяти аспектах [лечения старости].
I'm going to talk about why defeating aging is desirable.
Я расскажу, почему победа над старением желательна,
I'm going to talk about why we have to get our shit together,
почему мы должны собраться с духом
and actually talk about this a bit more than we do.
и, наконец, начать говорить эту тему.
I'm going to talk about feasibility as well, of course.
Я, конечно же, расскажу о возможностях реализации,
I'm going to talk about why we are so fatalistic
и о том, почему наш подход ко всей проблематике старения
about doing anything about aging.
пропитан фатализмом.
And then I'm going spend perhaps the second half of the talk
Вторая половина выступления будет посвящена
talking about, you know, how we might actually be able to prove that fatalism is wrong,
тому, чтобы доказать, что фатализм необоснован, и я сделаю это
namely, by actually doing something about it.
путём реального решения проблемы старения.
I'm going to do that in two steps.
Решение будет состоять из двух этапов. Я покажу